Model package for web app. it contains handler package; model_config package; core.py

handler package contains handler.py which contains ModelHandler, class for applying AI model.

model_config package contains dataset_preparation which contains history and method of creation dataset.
model_training package contains model_training.py for creating AI model. Also saves model, tokenizer and params into model_config/utils.
utils contains model, tokenizer and params

core.py initialises model handler for using below.
